<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
	<ServerGroup Name="VIKINGS MOD" Logo="https://i.postimg.cc/nr4wvf0n/VIKINGS-MOD.png">
		<!-- Logo is a direct link to a jpg /png file. Default image dimension is 2064x452 -->
		<Server Name="VIKINGSMOD">
			<Version>2.6</Version>
			<DownloadMode>Release</DownloadMode>
			<Downloads>
				<Download>https://github.com/NORDMANN845/VIKINGS-MOD/releases</Download>
				<AltDownload/>
			</Downloads>
			<!-- Got a website -->
			<WebSite>https://7daystodiemods.com/vikings-mod-coming-soon/</WebSite>
			<Description>
For 7D2D Version 2.6
Changelogs on Discord!
What exactly is the VIKINGS MOD?
The Vikings Mod is a massive overhaul for 7 Days to Die.  
You play as a survivor from the year 2026 who, together with your friends, was involved in a terrible car accident. 
All of your friends died in the crash - only you open your eyes again… but not in your own time.

You wake up in the year 845, weak, disoriented, and barely alive. From this moment on, survival becomes your only purpose. 
You must learn to live in the brutal world of the Viking Age, adapt to ancient traditions, and fight under the watchful eyes of the gods.

And unlike the original game, you won’t be fighting zombies.
In this world, your enemies are diseased Vikings, warriors driven mad and corrupted by a mysterious plague spreading across the land. They are faster, more aggressive, and far more unpredictable than anything you’ve faced before - and they will stop at nothing to tear you down.

You will experience 7 Days to Die in a completely new way.

As you progress, you follow in the footsteps of the legendary Lodbrok clan, uncovering their stories, their battles, and their legacy. Your journey will shape you into a true warrior - stronger, wiser, and closer to the gods.

Your ultimate goal is to rise in power and become as mighty as Odin himself. Only then will you be ready for the final challenge:
a boss battle against Fenrir, the monstrous wolf of the saga.

Defeat him, and your destiny is sealed - from that moment on, you will rule the land as a true Viking legend.		


IMPORTANT INFORMATION
-Not compatible with any other mods  
The Vikings Mod is a full overhaul and must be played without additional mods.

-Mod translation available in EN and DE only  
No other languages are supported at this time.

-Disable subtitles  
Subtitles should be turned off for the intended experience.

-Dynamic Music: OFF  
Please disable dynamic music in the audio settings.

-UI Transparency Settings  
Background: 95%
Foreground: 100%

VIKINGSMOD © NORDMANN
Forged in blood, steel, and relentless Viking craftsmanship.
All XML files, C# DLLs, code fragments, data structures, logic, textures,
icons, UI symbols, audio assets, and 3D models included in this mod
are the intellectual creation of Nordmann.
The contents of this mod may not be copied, reused, modified,
republished, or integrated into other mods or projects without
explicit permission from Jarl Nordmann.
Unauthorized use of these works is strictly forbidden.
</Description>
			<!-- Who made -->
			<Author>NORDMANN</Author>
			<!-- Have a discord you want people to join? -->
			<Discord>https://discord.gg/jkY7P4U39M </Discord>
			<!-- Want to give people an option to donate? -->
			<Donate>https://www.paypal.com/paypalme/goodfellasbc</Donate>
		</Server>
	</ServerGroup>
</Servers>
